Guide to the Eleanor Robson Belmont Papers
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series I: Correspondence, 1851-1980
  - Subseries I.1 Cataloged Correspondence, 1851-1979
    - Hewitt, Sarah Cooper, 1924-1928 (Box 7)
    - Heyward, Dorothy (Mrs. Dubose), February 1 (Box 7)
    - Hickey, Margaret, 1959-1975 (Box 7)
    - Hicks, Ellaline Terriss, undated (Box 7)
    - Hicks, Sir Seymour, undated (Box 7)
    - Higgins, O.L., 1925 September 8 (Box 7)
    - Hilles, Charles D., 1924-1949 (Box 7)
    - Hinshaw, David, 1951 April 16 (Box 7)
    - Hoffman, Malvina, 1941-1963 (Box 7)
    - Holtzmann, David Marshall, 1954 (Box 7)
    - Hoover, Herbert, 1928-1963 (Box 7)
    - Hoover, Lou Henry (Mrs. Herbert), 1932 (Box 7)
    - Hopkins, Archibald, undated (Box 7)
    - Hopkins, Charles, 1929 (Box 7)
    - Hopkins, Charlotte (Mrs. Archibald), August 3 (Box 7)
    - Hopkins, Harry L., 1922-1932 (Box 7)
    - Houghton, Alanson B., 1934-1935 (Box 7)
    - House, Edward Mandell, 1918-1936 (Box 7)
    - House, Loulie Hunter (Mrs. Edward M.), 1930 (Box 7)
    - Housman, Laurence, April 1 (Box 7)
    - Houston, David Franklin, 1930-1933 (Box 7)
    - Houston, Helen (Mrs. David F.), 1930 August 12 (Box 7)
    - Howard of Fenrith, Sir Esme William Howard, 1st Baron (1863-1939), 1928 February 8 (Box 7)
    - Howard, Harold Shafter, undated (Box 7)
    - Howard, Leslie, 1930 March 31 (Box 7)
    - Howe, Frederic C., 1937 April 19 (Box 7)
    - Howe, Mark Antony De Wolfe, 1953-1954 (Box 7)
    - Huber, Max, 1947 December 7 (Box 7)
    - Hughes, Antoinette Carter (Mrs. Charles E.), 1932 (Box 7)
    - Hughes, Charles Evans, 1933-1945 (Box 7)
    - Hull, Cordell, 1938 March 22 (Box 7)
    - Hurok, Sol, 1948 December 6 (Box 7)
    - Hurst, Fannie, 1938 September 30 (Box 7)
    - Hutchinson, John, 1904 January 4 (Box 7)
    - Hutchinson, Thomas, 1887 November 7 (Box 7)
    - Ingram, Jonas H., 1945 October 25 (Box 8)
    - Irving, Henry, 1904 September 20 (Box 8)
    - Isham, Margaret, 1928 (Box 8)
    - Jackson, Charles Douglas, 1960 May 3 (Box 8)
    - Jackson, William Alexander, 1960 October 10 (Box 8)
    - James, Henry, 1947 November 2 (Box 8)
    - James, Olivia Cutting, 1957-1960 (Box 8)
    - James, William, 1957 February 8 (Box 8)
    - Javits, Jacob K., 1978 December 12 (Box 8)
    - Jay, Dean, 1958 October 7 (Box 8)
    - Jenks, Mabel, undated (Box 8)
    - Jerome, Jerome Klapka, 1906-1913 (Box 8)
    - Johnson, Edward, 1937 November 20 (Box 8)
    - Johnson, Robert Underwood, 1915-1916 (Box 8)
    - Johnston, Eloise, 1938-1940 (Box 8)
    - Johnston, Mary, 1902-1924 (Box 8)
    - Jones, Mrs. Cadwalader, September 27 (Box 8)
    - Jones, Henry Arthur, undated (Box 8)
    - Jones, Jesse Holman, 1936-1943 (Box 8)
    - Jones, Robert Edmond, 1931 (Box 8)
    - Jones, Thomas, 1932 May 26 (Box 8)
    - Jones, Mrs. W.G., undated (Box 8)
    - Jusserand, Jean Adrien Antoine, 1914 November 16 (Box 8)
    - Kahn, Otto, 1931 February 6 (Box 8)
    - Kellogg, Paul U., 1918-1938 (Box 8)
    - Kelton, Laura, 1910 February 24 (Box 8)
    - Kennedy, Charles Rahn, 1904 September 19 (Box 8)
    - Keppel, Frederick Paul, 1922-1931 (Box 8)
    - Kerr, Phillip Henry, Marquess of Lothian, 1940 January 22 (Box 8)
    - Keyes, Frances Parkinson, 1953-1963 (Box 8)
    - King, John F., 1917-1918 (Box 8)
    - Kingman, John J., 1934 November 27 (Box 8)
    - Kinkaid, Helen, November 25 (Box 8)
    - Kirk, Alan Goodrich, undated (Box 8)
    - Kirk, Lydia, 1952-1953 (Box 8)
    - Koch, Edward I., 1978 November 30 (Box 8)
    - Kuhn, Walter, 1932 (Box 8)
    - La Farge, Christopher Grant, 1933-1936 (Box 8)
    - LaFarge, John, 1956-1959 (Box 8)
    - La Guardia, Fiorello, 1941 February 10 (Box 8)
    - Lambert, Tallmadge Augustine and Maud C., 1903 December 27 (Box 8)
    - Lamont, Florence (Mrs. Thomas William), undated (Box 8)
    - Lamont, Thomas, 1927-1947 (Box 8)
    - Lecomte du Nouy, Mary Bishop Harriman (Mrs. Pierre), June 22 (Box 8)
    - Lancaster, Albert Edward, 1904 (Box 8)
    - Lane, Anne W. (Mrs. Franklin Knight), 1926 January 10 (Box 8)
    - Lasky, Jesse L., 1914 October 19 (Box 8)
    - Laughlin, Clara Elizabeth, 1921 January 12 (Box 8)
    - Laurence, Bishop William, 1931-1940 (Box 8)
    - Lawrence, Robert, 1949 January 4 (Box 8)
    - Lee, Ruth (Mrs. Arthur Hamilton), undated (Box 8)
    - Leinsdorf, Erich, 1962 February 5 (Box 8)
    - Le Moyne, Sarah Cowell, 1902-1905 (Box 8)
    - Leroux, Hugues, 1918 December 17 (Box 8)
    - Lindberg, Anne Morrow (Mrs. Charles), 1933-1955 (Box 9)
    - Lindsay, John Vleit, 1967 November 10 (Box 9)
    - Lippman, Walter, 1960 July 28 (Box 9)
    - Locke, W. J., 1907 May 25 (Box 9)
    - Lodge, Emily Sears (Mrs. Henry Cabot Jr.), 1960 November 3 (Box 9)
    - Lodge, Henry Cabot (1850-1924) 1918 December 18 (Box 9)
    - Lodge, Henry Cabot Jr., 1957-1978 (Box 9)
    - Loeb, Louis, 1903-1904 (Box 9)
    - Loughran, John, 1909 May 5 (Box 9)
    - Lowell, Abbot Lawrence, 1934 September 10 (Box 9)
    - Lowell, Amy, 1916-1918 (Box 9)
    - Lowes, John Livingston, 1926 July 12 (Box 9)
    - Lubbock, Percy, 1917 October 12 (Box 9)
    - Lunt, Alfred and Lynne, undated (Box 9)
    - Lyttleton, Edith Balfour (Mrs. Alfred), 1917-1922 (Box 9)
    - McCall, Ella Esther (Mrs. Samuel W.), 1914 August 3À (Box 9)
    - McCall, Samuel Walker, 1916 August 2 (Box 9)
    - McCann, J. E., 1907 March 8 (Box 9)
    - McCarthy, E. M., 1918 January 18 (Box 9)
    - McCellan, G. M. S., 1904 January 28 (Box 9)
    - McClellan, George, 1904 September 8 (Box 9)
    - McClintic, Guthrie, 1924-1957 (Box 9)
    - McCloy, John J., 1957 February 19 (Box 9)
    - McCormick, Chauncey, 1951 December 28 (Box 9)
    - McCoy, Frances (Mrs. Frank R.), undated (Box 9)
    - McCoy, Frank Ross, 1940-1944 (Box 9)
    - McCrindle, Susan, 1949 December 4 (Box 9)
    - McGeachy, Mary Craig, 1937-1940 (Box 9)
    - McIntyre, Marvin Hunter, 1934 January 29 (Box 9)
    - Mack, Julian W., 1937 December 3 (Box 9)
    - MacKay, Clarence Hungerford, 1927 November 19 (Box 9)
    - McKenna, Reginald, 1930-1938 (Box 9)
    - MacKinnon, A. E., undated (Box 9)
    - McLean, Archibald, 1904 October 27 (Box 9)
    - MacLeish, Ada (Mrs. Archibald), 1956-1957 (Box 9)
    - MacLeish, Archibald, 1940-1978 (Box 9)
    - MacLeod, Josephine, 1936 (Box 9)
    - MacVeagh, Franklin, 1911 December 18 (Box 9)
    - Maeterlinck, Maurice, 1913 July 22 (Box 9)
    - Malcolm, Jeanne, 1939 November 5 (Box 9)
    - Mansfield, Beatrice (Mrs. Richard), 1902 January 4 (Box 9)
    - Mansfield, Richard, undated (Box 9)
    - Mantell, Robert Bruce, 1914 November 1 (Box 9)
    - Marbury, Elisabeth, 1905-1923 (Box 9)
    - Marquand, John, May 24 (Box 9)
    - Marshall, George C., 1943-1951 (Box 9)
    - Marshall, Katherine Boyce Tupper Brown (Mrs. George C.), 1942-1950 (Box 9)
    - Marvin, Mary, undated (Box 9)
    - Masaryk, Alice G., 1938 June (Box 9)
    - Masefield, John, undated (Box 9)
    - Masefield, Richard, 1905 April 1 (Box 9)
    - Mason, Julian S., 1932 (Box 9)
    - Masters, Edgar Lee, 1929 (Box 9)
    - Mathison, Edith Wynne (Kennedy), 1904-1914 (Box 9)
    - Matthews, Brander, 1922 January 30 (Box 9)
    - Matthews, William Henry, 1936 October 14 (Box 9)
    - Maude, Cyril, 1904 November 10 (Box 9)
    - Mayo, Katherine, 1928-1940 (Box 9)
    - Megrue, Roi Cooper, 1912 May 19 (Box 9)
    - Melchior, Lauritz, 1936-1948 (Box 9)
    - Miller, Alice Duer, April 5 (Box 9)
    - Mitchell, Grant, 1927 October 26 (Box 9)
    - Montague, Gilbert H., 1951-1953 (Box 9)
    - Monteagle, Thomas Aubrey Spring Rice, 3rd Baron, 1917 September 15 (Box 9)
    - Moore, Gertrude, 1927 November 5 (Box 9)
    - Moore, Marianne, 1955 August 17 (Box 9)
    - Moore, Robert Walton, 1940 November 19 (Box 9)
    - Morawetz, Marjorie Nott (Mrs. Victor), undated (Box 9)
    - Morgan, Charles, 1941 October 6 (Box 9)
    - Morgan, Constance Cutter Morrow (Mrs. Aubrey Niel), September 21 (Box 9)
    - Morgan, Henry, June 21 (Box 9)
    - Morgan, Hilda (Mrs. Charles), 1941-1944 (Box 9)
    - Morgan, John Pierpont, 1912-1935 (Box 9)
    - Morison, Samuel Eliot, 1963-1976 (Box 9)
    - Morris, Clara, undated (Box 10)
    - Morris, William, undated (Box 10)
    - Morrow, Dwight Whitney, 1919-1931 (Box 10)
    - Morrow, Elizabeth Reeve Cutter (Mrs. Dwight W.), 1933-1954 (Box 10)
    - Moses, Robert, 1943-1978 (Box 10)
    - Munsey, Frank Andrew, 1923-1924 (Box 10)
    - Murphy, Adah C. Woodworth (Mrs. J. Francis), 1904 (Box 10)
    - Murphy, Grayson M. P., undated (Box 10)
    - Nazimova, Alla, 1919 October 3 (Box 10)
    - Neilson, Anne Perry Rodgers (Mrs. Louis), 1943 (Box 10)
    - Nethersole, Olga, 1904-1909 (Box 10)
    - Nevins, Allan, 1950 February (Box 10)
    - Newton, A. Edward, 1930 February 24-26 (Box 10)
    - Norman, Priscilla Reyntiens Norman, Baroness, undated (Box 10)
    - Norman, Priscilla Cecilia Maria Worsthorne (Mrs. Montagu Collet), undated (Box 10)
    - Norton, Charles D., 1922 (Box 10)
    - Norton, Katherine McKim Garrison (Mrs. Charles Dyer), March 21 (Box 10)
    - Novotna, Yarmila, 1957 December 5 (Box 10)
    - O'Brien, Morgan J., 1926 April 14 (Box 10)
    - O'Higgins, Harvey, 1917 June 2 (Box 10)
    - Orcutt, Louie Thompson (Mrs. William Dana), May 6 (Box 10)
    - Ormandy, Eugene, 1955 October 20 (Box 10)
    - Osborn, Henry Fairfield, 1932 July 16 (Box 10)
    - Osborn, Margaret, March 7 (Box 10)
    - O'Shaughnessy, Nelson, undated (Box 10)
    - Paderewski, Ignacy Jan, 1922-1936 (Box 10)
    - Palmer, Frederick, 1923-1924 (Box 10)
    - Parker, Louis Napoleon, 1903-1918 (Box 10)
    - Parry, David, December 4 (Box 10)
    - Parsons, William B., 1960 June 28 (Box 10)
    - Patterson, Robert P., 1950 December 15 (Box 10)
    - Peabody, Josephine Preston, October 3 (Box 10)
    - Peirce, Walter T., 1903 May 22 (Box 10)
    - Pemberton, Brock, 1928 November 16 (Box 10)
    - Pepper, George Wharton, 1932-1951 (Box 10)
    - Perkins, Frances, 1934-1939 (Box 10)
    - Perkins, James H., 1928 July 17 (Box 10)
    - Pershing, John Joseph, 1923-1939 (Box 10)
    - Phelps, William Lyon, 1940 (Box 10)
    - Phillips, Caroline (Mrs. William), undated (Box 10)
      (s.)
    - Phillips, David Graham, undated (Box 10)
    - Phillips, Stephen, 1913 August 4 (Box 10)
    - Phillips, William, 1935 January 30 (Box 10)
    - Pike, Irene Mervyn Parnicott Pike, Baroness, 1975 July (Box 10)
    - Pinero, Arthur Wing, 1904-1917 (Box 10)
    - Pinero, Myra (Mrs. Arthur Wing), December 14 (Box 10)
    - Plympton, Eben, 1914 November 13 (Box 10)
    - Poole, Ernest, 1916-1924 (Box 10)
    - Potter, C. Bronson, undated (Box 10)
    - Potter, Charles Francis, 1940 November 23 (Box 10)
    - Price, Leontyne, December (Box 10)
    - Price, Walter W., 1928 October 4 (Box 10)
    - Procope, Hjalmar J., 1939 April 28 (Box 10)
    - Prosser, Seward, 1922-1931 (Box 10)
    - Pryor, Sara A., 1910 February 25 (Box 10)
    - Pupin, Michael I., 1928-1931 (Box 10)
    - Randall, Ollie A., 1953 December 19 (Box 10)
    - Rathbone, Eleazar, 1932 April 23 (Box 10)
    - Reading, Stella Charnaud Isaacs, Marchioness of, 1958-1971 (Box 10)
    - Redfield, William C., 1919 April (Box 10)
    - Reese, Lizette Woodworth, 1928 February 6 (Box 10)
    - Rehan, Ada, 1914 November (Box 10)
    - Reid, Elizabeth Mills, 1917-1920 (Box 10)
    - Reid, Helen Rogers, 1931-1937 (Box 10)
    - Reiner, Fritz, 1953 April 12 (Box 10)
    - Rhodes, Harrison, undated (Box 10)
    - Rice, Alice Hegan, 1904-1933 (Box 10)
    - Rives, Reginald W., 1942 August 12 (Box 10)
    - Roberts, Charles G. D., 1902 February 6 (Box 10)
    - Roberts, Mary M., undated (Box 10)
    - Roberts, Owen J., 1951 September 18 (Box 10)
    - Robinson, Corinne Roosevelt, 1916-1930 (Box 10)
    - Robinson, Edwin Arlington, 1928 (Box 11)
    - Robinson, Theodore Douglas, 1924 (Box 11)
    - Roche, Charles, 1904 December 8 (Box 11)
    - Rockefeller, Abby A., undated (Box 11)
    - Rockefeller, John Davison, 1928-1956 (Box 11)
    - Rockefeller, John Davison, 3rd., 1969 April (Box 11)
    - Rockefeller, Martha B., 1952-1961 (Box 11)
    - Rodgers, Robert Perry, 1933 (Box 11)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A., 1959 March 2 (Box 11)
    - Rodin, August e, 1902 June 12 (Box 11)
    - Rogers, John William, 1927 May (Box 11)
    - Romulo, Carlos P., 1949-1962 (Box 11)
    - Romulo, Virginia (Mrs. Carlos), September (Box 11)
    - Roosevelt, Archibald, 1930-1963 (Box 11)
    - Roosevelt, Christine Kean (Mrs. William Emlen), December 17 (Box 11)
    - Roosevelt, Edith Kermit, 1923-1944 (Box 11)
    - Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1931-1959 (Box 11)
    - Roosevelt, Elliott, 1891 January 15 (Box 11)
    - Roosevelt, Franklin D., 1935 October 30 (Box 11)
    - Roosevelt, Laura, undated (Box 11)
    - Roosevelt, Nicholas, 1950 December (Box 11)
    - Roosevelt, Sara Delano, undated (Box 11)
    - Roosevelt, Theodore, 1912-1918 (Box 11)
    - Rose, Edward, 1904 (Box 11)
    - Rothschild, Anthony Gustav de (1887-1961), 1931 July 19 (Box 11)
    - Rothschild, Marie Perugia (Mrs. Leopold de) (1862-19370 1914 April 27 (Box 11)
    - Rouland, Minnie T. Dwight (Mrs. Orlando), 1909 December 30 (Box 11)
    - Roussy de Sales, Odette Butruille de, 1940 October (Box 11)
    - Rowe, Leo S., 1931 January 23 (Box 11)
    - Russell, Ada Dwyer, 1908-1945 (Box 11)
    - Russell, Annie, 1914 November 23 (Box 11)
    - Russell, George Grossmilk, 1904 September 8 (Box 11)
    - Russell, George W. (A.E.), 1935 July 5 (Box 11)
    - Ryan, Thomas F., January 22 (Box 11)
    - Sabin, Pauline Morton (Mrs. Charles H.), 1931 February 3 (Box 11)
    - Salisbury, Leah, 1938 May 10 (Box 11)
    - Salter, (James) Arthur Salter, Baron, undated (Box 11)
    - Sanders, Mary E., undated (Box 11)
    - Sargent, Eunice W. (Mrs. Fitzwilliam), 1929 (Box 11)
    - Sarnoff, David, 1937-1951 (Box 11)
    - Sarton, May,1974-1975 (Box 11)
    - Sawyer, Kathleen B., undated (Box 11)
    - Schaefer, Clara (Mrs. Ludwig), 1953 November 17 (Box 11)
    - Scheff, Fritzi (Mrs. John Fox), April 14 (Box 11)
    - Schelling, Ernest, undated (Box 11)
    - Schmidt, Fritz L., Jr., 1922 January 2 (Box 11)
    - Scott, Elizabeth, 1930 October 3 (Box 11)
    - Scott, Geoffrey, 1929 (Box 11)
    - Scott, Mary (Mrs. Charles), May 14 (Box 11)
    - Seabury, William Marston, 1934 June 28 (Box 11)
    - Sellers, David Foote, 1937 (Box 12)
    - Sevareid, Eric, 1955-1959 (Box 12)
    - Seymour, Gladys (Mrs. Whitney North), undated (Box 12)
    - Seymour, May, November 24 (Box 12)
    - Sharp, Hallie Clough, January 1 (Box 12)
    - Shaw, Albert, 1945 November 2 (Box 12)
    - Shaw, Charlotte Frances Payne-Townshend (Mrs. George Bernard), 1906-1917 (Box 12)
    - Shaw, George Bernard, 1904-1914 (Box 12)
    - Sheean, Diana Forbes-Robertson (Mrs. Vincent), 1959-1960 (Box 12)
    - Sheldon, Edward, undated (Box 12)
    - Sheppard, Jeanie Rumsey (Mrs. John S.), 1932 August 17 (Box 12)
    - Sherman, Julia C., 1909 February 16 (Box 12)
    - Sills, Beverly, 1975 May 29 (Box 12)
    - Simonson, Lee, 1947-1948 (Box 12)
    - Skinner, Cornelia Otis, undated (Box 12)
    - Skinner, Maud Durbin (Mrs. Otis), 1929-1936 (Box 12)
    - Skinner, Otis, 1904 (Box 12)
    - Sleath-Skelton, Ellis (Jefferies), undated (Box 12)
    - Smalley, George, 1905-1915 (Box 12)
    - Smith, Alfred E., 1932-1934 (Box 12)
    - Smith, Corinna (Mrs. Joseph L.), 1957 February 7 (Box 12)
    - Smith, Joseph Lindon, 1931 March 23 (Box 12)
    - Sothern, Edward Hugh, 1920-1921 (Box 12)
    - Spofford, Charles, 1949 (Box 12)
    - Squire, John C., 1926-1934 (Box 12)
    - Stanley, Arthur, 1920-1939 (Box 12)
    - Steed, Henry Wickham, 1932 April 2 (Box 12)
    - Steinhardt, Maxwell, 1955 March 2 (Box 12)
    - Steinway, Theodore E., 1951 February (Box 12)
    - Sterner, Albert, 1912 September 22 (Box 12)
    - Stettinius, Edward R., 1944 December 30 (Box 12)
    - Stevens, Rise (Surovy), 1959-1978 (Box 12)
    - Stevenson, Burton E., 1922-1923 (Box 12)
    - Stevenson, Elizabeth B. (Mrs. Burton E.), 1922 (Box 12)
    - Stillemans, Rev. J. F., 1914 December 15 (Box 12)
    - Stimson, Henry, 1932-1945 (Box 12)
    - Stimson, Mabel (Mrs. Henry L.), undated (Box 12)
    - Stokowski, Leopold, 1935-1936 (Box 12)
    - Story, Douglas, 1904 September 27 (Box 12)
    - Stotesbury, Louis W., 1924 February 27 (Box 12)
    - Straight, Willard Dickerman, undated (Box 12)
    - Straten-Ponthoz, Robert van der, 1938 January 3 (Box 12)
    - Straus, Jesse Isidor, 1932 January 12 (Box 12)
    - Strauss, Frederick, 1931-1936 (Box 12)
    - Strauss, Lewis L., 1952-1956 (Box 12)
    - Streeter, Edward, 1930 December 22 (Box 12)
    - Streeter, John W., 1902-1904 (Box 12)
    - Strindberg, Frida Ulm (Mrs. August ), undated (Box 12)
    - Strode, Hudson, 1957 (Box 12)
    - Strong, Austin, 1933-1951 (Box 12)
    - Strong, Mary (Mrs. Austin), 1923-1948 (Box 12)
    - Sulzberger, Arthur Hays, 1940-1961 (Box 12)
    - Sulzberger, Iphigene Ochs (Mrs. Arthur H.), 1977-1979 (Box 12)
    - Swing, Raymond Gram, 1931 July 29 (Box 12)
    - Swope, Herbert Bayard, 1923 November 27 (Box 12)
    - Taft, William Howard, 1921 November 2 (Box 12)
    - Tarbell, Ida M., 1940 (Box 12)
    - Tarkington, Booth, 1913 October 14 (Box 12)
    - Tarkington, Laurel Louisa (Mrs. Booth), 1907 December 22 (Box 12)
    - Taylor, Deems, 1935 October 16 (Box 12)
    - Taylor, Maxwell D., 1961 May 2 (Box 12)
    - Taylor, Myron C., 1931-1953 (Box 12)
    - Taylor, Wayne C., 1945 December 15 (Box 12)
    - Tempest, Marie, undated (Box 12)
    - Templewood, (Lady) Maud Lygon Hoare, Viscountess (1882-1962), 1949 December (Box 12)
    - Ten Broeck, Dirck, 1804 July 12 (Box 12)
    - Terry, Ellen, 1913 January 8 (Box 13)
    - Terry, Phyllis Neilson, undated (Box 13)
    - Teyte, Maggie, undated (Box 13)
    - Thackrey, Ted O., 1940 December 3 (Box 13)
    - Thomas, August us, 1916 February 2 (Box 13)
    - Thompson, Dorothy (Lewis), 1937 October 25 (Box 13)
    - Thomson, Virgil, undated (Box 13)
    - Thorndike, Sybil, undated (Box 13)
    - Tiedemann, T.H.A., 1934 August 13 (Box 13)
    - Tiffany, Isabel Bolton Perry (Mrs. George) (1834-1912), undated (Box 13)
    - Tiffany, Olive (Mrs. Perry), 1943 September 2 (Box 13)
    - Todd, John R., 1936 June 26 (Box 13)
    - Towne, Charles Hanson, 1922 October (Box 13)
    - Train, Arthur, 1921 January (Box 13)
    - Tree, Herbert Beerbohm, 1904-1915 (Box 13)
    - Tree, Maud (Mrs. Herbert Beerbohm), undated (Box 13)
    - Troubetzkoy, Amelie, undated (Box 13)
    - Truman, Bess W. (Mrs. Harry S.), 1945 À-1946 (Box 13)
    - Tucker, Richard (Mr. and Mrs.), 1972 August 17 (Box 13)
    - Turner, Marion A., 1917 November 19 (Box 13)
    - Tyler, George C., 1902-1935 (Box 13)
    - Van Doren, Irita, 1957 (Box 13)
    - Van Fleet, Helen (Mrs. James), 1951-1953 (Box 13)
    - Van Gelder, P., 1924 February 14 (Box 13)
    - Vaughan, Bernard, 1912 March 10 (Box 13)
    - Vincent, George E., 1920 (Box 13)
    - Wadsworth, Eliot, 1919-1959 (Box 13)
    - Wadsworth, John, 1914 November 1 (Box 13)
    - Wadsworth, Nancy (Whitman) Scull (Mrs. Eliot), 1935 August 19 (Box 13)
    - Wakehurst, Margaret, 1949-1950 (Box 13)
    - Wald, Lillian D., 1927-1935 (Box 13)
    - Wallace, Lila Bell Acheson (Mrs. DeWitt), 1972 June 12 (Box 13)
    - Walpole, Hugh, 1926 (Box 13)
    - Walter, Bruno, 1953 (Box 13)
    - Walworth, Arthur, 1948 June 25 (Box 13)
    - Ward, Dorothy, 1904 October 14 (Box 13)
    - Ward, Mary August a (Mrs. Humphrey), 1903-1917 (Box 13)
    - Wardwell, Allen, 1946 February 16 (Box 13)
    - Warfield, David, 1914 November 12 (Box 13)
    - Warren, Whitney, 1914 July 1 (Box 13)
    - Wavell, Eugenie, 1949 (Box 13)
    - Webster, Daniel, 1851 June 15 (Box 13)
    - Webster, Margaret, April 6 (Box 13)
    - Wells, Carolyn (Houghton), 1904-1933 (Box 13)
    - Wells, Herbert George, 1931 October 24 (Box 13)
    - Wenlock, (Dame) Annie Allen Cunard Lawley, Baroness, undated (Box 13)
    - Wenner-Gren, Marguerite G., undated (Box 13)
    - Weston, Florence, 1909 November 25 (Box 13)
    - Wetmore, Maude, September 28 (Box 13)
    - Wharton, Edith, 1914-1919 (Box 13)
    - White, Emily Vanderbilt (Mrs. Henry), December 31 (Box 13)
    - White, Henry, 1920-1924 (Box 13)
    - White, Lawrence Grant, 1937 January 8 (Box 13)
    - White, Robert, 1947 August 28 (Box 13)
    - Whitney, Gertrude Vanderbilt, undated (Box 13)
    - Whitney, John Hay, 1951-1952 (Box 14)
    - Whyte, Alexander Frederick, undated (Box 14)
    - Whyte, Margaret (Mrs. Alexander F.), July 16 (Box 14)
    - Wickersham, George W., 1924-1933 (Box 14)
    - Wicks, Pembroke, 1917 October 1 (Box 14)
    - Wiggin, Kate Douglas (Mrs. George Riggs), 1914-1915 (Box 14)
    - Wilder, Thornton, 1928-1959 (Box 14)
    - Wiley, Louis, 1930 September 10 (Box 14)
    - Wilson, Francis, 1914 November 25 (Box 14)
    - Wilson, Woodrow, 1920 December 19 (Box 14)
    - Winant, John Gilbert, 1937 December 14 (Box 14)
    - Winthrop, Henry Rogers, 1939 March 3 (Box 14)
    - Wise, Stephen S., 1918 May 20 (Box 14)
    - Wiseman, (Sir) William George Eden, 1931 March 25 (Box 14)
    - Wister, Owen, 1927 (Box 14)
    - Wohlforth, Robert, 1957 (Box 14)
    - Wolcott, Frances M., 1909-1920 (Box 14)
    - Wolfe, Paul, 1955 April 13 (Box 14)
    - Wood, Leonard, 1915-1918 (Box 14)
    - Wood, Louise A., undated (Box 14)
    - Woolley, Katharine, 1929-1932 (Box 14)
    - Woolley, Leonard, 1929-1931 (Box 14)
    - Wrench, Evelyn, 1932 (Box 14)
    - Wrong, Joyce, March 3 (Box 14)
    - Wylie, A. E., January 21 (Box 14)
    - Yeats, William Butler, undated (Box 14)
    - Young, Owen D., 1931-1936 (Box 14)
    - Young, Lillian Nordica, 1910 March 10 (Box 14)
    - Young, Stark, 1923-1925 (Box 14)
    - Yourcenar, Marguerite, 1960-1978 (Box 14)
    - Zangwill, Edith (Mrs. Israel), 1904-1933 (Box 14)
    - Zangwill, Israel, 1904-1924 (Box 14)
    - Zangwill, Oliver L., 1957 November 15 (Box 14)
  - Subseries I.2 Arranged Correspondence, 1908-1980
    The arranged correspondence consists of general correspondence, especially greeting cards. Mrs. Belmont was close to her husband's extended family and there is a good deal of correspondence from various Belmont relatives.
    - A-Z and unidentified (Box 14-17)
    - Family Correspondence (Box 14-17)
- Series II: Subject Files, 1904-1979
  The subject files relate to the Belmont family and Mrs. Belmont's philanthropic causes. There are extensive files on August Belmont's estate which have information on the New York Subway, the Belmont racing stables, and the several properties. Other files reflect Mrs. Belmont's interest in Belmont genealogy and her pride in the Belmont connection to Commodore Perry. There is extensive documentation on the organizations with which Mrs. Belmont was associated including the American Shakespeare Festival Foundation, the Metropolitan Opera Association, the Community Service Society, Unemployment Relief, and the Red Cross. There are also files related to her theatrical life including a file on George Bernard Shaw, Israel Zangwill, and Frances Hodgson Burnett. Included are drafts of her speeches, her autobiography, and her play, In the Next Room. The files are arranged alphabetically by subject.
  - Adopt-a-family, 1940-1954 (Box 17)
  - American Women of Achievement Award, 1940-1951 (Box 17)
  - Appointment calendars, 1968-1978 (Box 18)
  - Belmont
    - Estate, 1926-1972 (Box 19)
    - Financial papers, 1954-1976 (Box 19)
    - Horses and horse-breeding, 1931-1966 (Box 19)
    - Household furnishings, 1912-1963 (Box 19)
    - Inventories and lists, 1928-1977 (Box 19)
    - Nursery Farm-Babylon, 1916-1939 (Box 19)
    - Gladbrook Farm, New Ashford, MA, 1929 (Box 20)
    - Syosset, Long Island, New York, 1927-1957 (Box 20)
    - Wills, Belmont family history (Box 20)
    - Letters to relatives (Box 20)
    - IRT and Railroad (Box 20)
  - Belmont Family Memorabilia (Box 21)